duckworth-lewis.com 2014-09-02

# The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 > Home

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 does not read any of your private online communications.

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 and The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 collects and uses your personal information to operate the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web site and deliver the services you have requested. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 and its affiliates. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20, in order to determine what The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 pages, or register with The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 site or services, a cookie helps The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 is protecting your information.

Contact Information

The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Duckworth Lewis Method - The Duckworth Lewis Calculator for ODI and T20 at [ryan@duckworth-lewis.com](mailto:ryan@duckworth-lewis.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
